​​​ ​I've gathered fifty YouTube LEGENDS​ ​​
​​​ ​wooOOOOoOO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​and whoever leaves this cube last​ ​​
​​​ ​wins a MILLION dollars ​ ​​
​​ ​for their subscribers!​ ​​
​​​ ​These creators built YouTube ​ ​​
​​ ​into what it is today.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're responsible for some of ​ ​​
​​ ​the most viral videos in history,​ ​​
​​​ ​and they're all going head-to-head ​ ​​
​​ ​for the first time ever​ ​​
​​​ ​to win one million dollars ​ ​​
​​ ​for their subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Feels like a reunion.​ ​​
​​​ ​Some of these people, ​ ​​
​​ ​I haven't seen for over a decade.​ ​​
​​​ ​These are like the Speed and Kai Cenats, ​ ​​
​​ ​but of like ten years ago.​ ​​
​​​ ​At leaaaast ten years ago.​ ​​
​​​ ​FIFTEEN years ago!!​ ​​
​​​ ​huh HUAH HAHAHA!​ ​​
​​​ ​ha ha HAAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you were to grab my computer ​ ​​
​​ ​when I was seventeen,​ ​​
​​​ ​and look at all the channels ​ ​​
​​ ​that I subscribed to,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's basically this cube.​ ​​
​​​ ​When I was a small YouTuber, ​ ​​
​​ ​I tried to join FaZe​ ​​
​​​ ​and you didn't let me in.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we fumbled the bag there…​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I join now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Um…​ ​​
​​​ ​At one point you, were the fifth most ​ ​​
​​ ​subscribed to channel on all of YouTube.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm probably the biggest ​ ​​
​​ ​fall-off in this whole box.​ ​​
​​​ ​Maybe EVER.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think ever.​ ​​
​​​ ​Fred here was the first channel to hit ​ ​​
​​ ​a million subscribers on YouTube.​ ​​
​​​ ​HEYYY, it's Fred!!​ ​​
​​​ ​If they haven't unsubscribed by now, ​ ​​
​​ ​they deserve a million.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys watch Fortnite videos,​ ​​
​​​ ​but back in the day we used to watch ​ ​​
​​ ​Call of Duty videos.​ ​​
​​​ ​YeaaAAahh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​These guys RANNN YouTube 15 years ago.​ ​​
​​​ ​Chad is one of the co-founders of YouTube.​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't become more legendary than that.​ ​​
​​​ ​I created the stage, and ​ ​​
​​ ​they brought the talent.​ ​​
​​​ ​Without these creators, ​ ​​
​​ ​I wouldn't be where I am today.​ ​​
​​​ ​So to celebrate us hitting ​ ​​
​​ ​500 million subscribers,​ ​​
​​​ ​this is my way of giving back to those ​ ​​
​​ ​who inspired me.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you didn't make YouTube,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd be working at Walmart right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!! Let's get this started!​ ​​
​​​ ​CHANGE THE FLOOR!!​ ​​
​​​ ​In front of you are five Lamborghinis,​ ​​
​​​ ​one of which is made of cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​whoOAAAA!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHh, that's cool!​ ​​
​​​ ​To move on, just choose ​ ​​
​​ ​one of the real Lamborghinis.​ ​​
​​​ ​OPEee!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're goin'!​ ​​
​​​ ​They didn't even let me finish.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, be careful which spot you choose,​ ​​
​​​ ​because if you choose ​ ​​
​​ ​the cake Lamborghini,​ ​​
​​​ ​you'll be eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Five looks like CAKE!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Five TOTALLYYY looks like cake, no??​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm goin' three.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, three is NOT cake?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gotta be four!! ​ ​​
​​ ​I think it's four.​ ​​
​​​ ​Brooo, I cannot tell.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't either.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't tell!​ ​​
​​​ ​Four! Four.​ ​​
​​​ ​Four!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think four is cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it's two…​ ​​
​​​ ​NAHh, five's cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​How are you feeling about ​ ​​
​​ ​number three?​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel good, if I---​ ​​
​​​ ​Three doesn't look like cake…?​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​Why you say it like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​There is NO way to tell.​ ​​
​​​ ​There are ways to tell.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah?​ ​​
​​​ ​Jimmy, I have a red Lambo, ​ ​​
​​ ​and I can't tell.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoever did this is a perfectionist.​ ​​
​​​ ​They all look SOO real.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know anything about ​ ​​
​​ ​Lamborghinis or cars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah?​ ​​
​​​ ​But I know cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​Number two is lookin' ​ ​​
​​ ​particularly delicious.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's something about ​ ​​
​​ ​the reflection of number two,​ ​​
​​​ ​which is where I am, ​ ​​
​​ ​that gives me great concernnn.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why do you think that? Why?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's four, Jimmy. It's four.​ ​​
​​​ ​The windows are not as shiny ​ ​​
​​ ​as the other ones.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're not reflecting the light ​ ​​
​​ ​as much as the other ones.​ ​​
​​​ ​The windows are like, not quite right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Something-- Something's off.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are we cooked on four?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think we are cooked on four.​ ​​
​​​ ​And when Corridor Digital got off ​ ​​
​​ ​their spot for a closer look,​ ​​
​​​ ​somebody noticed…​ ​​
​​​ ​And took the opportunity.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​YESS!​ ​​
​​​ ​WAITT!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, he switched with you!!​ ​​
​​​ ​He took it--?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, that's fine.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't believe you've done this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which sparked Roman Atwood ​ ​​
​​ ​to steal a spot,​ ​​
​​​ ​followed by Dude Perfect.​ ​​
​​​ ​ohHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​YESSSS!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Four is cake.​ ​​
​​​ ​I just got saaaaved.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which led to Philip DeFranco ​ ​​
​​ ​stealing a spot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, SNAP!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is everyone good with their picks?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, anyone want the cake line?​ ​​
​​​ ​ahh HAH HAAaaa!!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, let's find out which ​ ​​
​​ ​one of you will be eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it TWO?!​ ​​
​​​ ​WAAITT, wait, WAIT!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which one? Which one?​ ​​
​​​ ​WHICH ONE IS IT???​ ​​
​​​ ​Five is NOT cake!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gonna be TWO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, NOOOooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no. It's FOUR!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's FOURRR!​ ​​
​​​ ​OH, no! NOOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OhhHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHHhhHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​yESS!!​ ​​
​​​ ​wooOOOoo!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOOOooooOO--​ ​​
​​​ ​oooOOOOoooHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​We KNEW it was the wrong one,​ ​​
​​​ ​but we were TRAPPED here!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHA HAA HA HAAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​It looked kind of tasty, so I didn't know.​ ​​
​​​ ​ohh, NOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​You have all now been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​agHHhhahhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​And for those of you that remain,​ ​​
​​​ ​your teams for the next game ​ ​​
​​ ​have now been decided.​ ​​
​​​ ​CHANGE THE FLOOOOR!​ ​​
​​​ ​You are now all teammates.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think you can tell​ ​​
​​​ ​we're gonna be taking a trip ​ ​​
​​ ​down memory lane.​ ​​
​​​ ​What are some other big trends ​ ​​
​​ ​that helped shape YouTube?​ ​​
​​​ ​SLIMEEE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ice BUCKET!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Cinnamon challenge??​ ​​
​​​ ​BRING it on in!​ ​​
​​​ ​We can't do a OG YouTube video…​ ​​
​​​ ​without water bottle flips!​ ​​
​​​ ​wooaahhHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​YOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh, I'm SOO good at that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Arguably one of the biggest trends ​ ​​
​​ ​in YouTube history.​ ​​
​​​ ​My kids play bottle flip.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you-- you kinda know this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​As long as you don't go up there and ​ ​​
​​ ​choke in front of everybody,​ ​​
​​​ ​you'll be gooood.​ ​​
​​​ ​Dude Perfect has over a billion views ​ ​​
​​ ​on water bottle flip trick shots.​ ​​
​​​ ​What advice do you have ​ ​​
​​ ​for your team?​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I was tellin' him​ ​​
​​​ ​the worst thing you can do is ​ ​​
​​ ​under-rotate the bottle.​ ​​
​​​ ​One at a timeee, someone from ​ ​​
​​ ​your team's gonna come up​ ​​
​​​ ​until they land a water bottle flip.​ ​​
​​​ ​The first three teams ​ ​​
​​ ​to have all ten players​ ​​
​​​ ​land a water bottle on ​ ​​
​​ ​this table will move on.​ ​​
​​​ ​The final team will be eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, SHOOT!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whyyy?​ ​​
​​​ ​Always something, Jimmy.​ ​​
​​​ ​ooohh!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!!​ ​​
​​​ ​GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go, Roman!!​ ​​
​​​ ​GOOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You GOT this, Roman!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHH! All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Got it!!​ ​​
​​​ ​yESS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go, go, go, go! ​ ​​
​​ ​Go, go, GO, GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Green's fallin' behind!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're good, Roman! ​ ​​
​​ ​No sweat.​ ​​
​​​ ​Got it.​ ​​
​​​ ​yeaAHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​NICE, nice!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Every team is on the board with one.​ ​​
​​​ ​YESS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Blue pulls to the lead.​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAAaaHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!!​ ​​
​​​ ​COME ON, Casey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Casey, let's do it. ​ ​​
​​ ​I grew up watching your vlogs.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're a big inspiration for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jimmy, you're DISTRACTING me!​ ​​
​​​ ​Casey, you're letting childhood me down!​ ​​
​​​ ​You were my HERO when I was a kid.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why can't you land a water bottle flip?​ ​​
​​​ ​THERE we go!!​ ​​
​​​ ​waaAAAHHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​YESS!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NICE!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, LET'S GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, COME ONN!​ ​​
​​​ ​YES!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go, let's go, LET'S GO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​And just like that, orange takes the lead.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're cookin'!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Lloyd from ​ ​​
​​ ​Epic Rap Battles of History.​ ​​
​​​ ​Bro, we used to jam out to those ​ ​​
​​ ​in my middle school.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahh, we all jammed!!​ ​​
​​​ ​More flick!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it. You got it!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, yes!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NICE!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo, let's GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go, let's go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go, let's go, let's gooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange is almost done.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is Evan Fong from Vanoss. ​ ​​
​​ ​He makes music now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I play one of your songs?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, you can.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here, play one of his songs.​ ​​
​​​ ​GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! YEAHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes! YESSS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Vanoss is really struggling right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​More flick!​ ​​
​​​ ​MORE FLICK!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Little more!!​ ​​
​​​ ​More flick on the wrist.​ ​​
​​​ ​Just DO it!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YESSss!​ ​​
​​​ ​GO, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is soooo freaking STRESSful.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Chad!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nice! NICE! NICEEE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's go, CHAD!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go, go, go!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Blue team, you're in last place.​ ​​
​​​ ​GO, GO, GO, GOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Last one, Ali-A!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on… ​ ​​
​​ ​You're letting me down.​ ​​
​​​ ​THERE we go!​ ​​
​​​ ​They're back in this now, ​ ​​
​​ ​but orange only has one left.​ ​​
​​​ ​Stronger, stronger, STRONGER!!​ ​​
​​​ ​There we goooo!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange team is MOVIN' on!!​ ​​
​​​ ​woooOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Elephant toothpaste?​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOOoooOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Orange team is MOVIN' on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Keep going!​ ​​
​​​ ​Two more teams still move on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Green is at seven now, back to back,​ ​​
​​​ ​and pink is right behind them!​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ Chocolate raiiinnnn… ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​OOOHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you good?​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you sure you're good?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm good, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, let me know if you need anything.​ ​​
​​​ ​YES!!​ ​​
​​​ ​GOOO! Go, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Eva, you HAVE to land this now​ ​​
​​​ ​if you want to give ​ ​​
​​ ​your team a chance.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yo, GUYS!! ​ ​​
​​ ​Hurry up, man!​ ​​
​​​ ​Tick, tick, tick, tick!​ ​​
​​​ ​MORE flick!​ ​​
​​​ ​MOREEE flick!!​ ​​
​​​ ​EVAAaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's not flipping enough!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come ONNN!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got this!!​ ​​
​​​ ​yeaHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Green has one left.​ ​​
​​​ ​YES!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this more stressful than ​ ​​
​​ ​reporting the news?​ ​​
​​​ ​YEP.​ ​​
​​​ ​Pink has two left.​ ​​
​​​ ​More FLIP!​ ​​
​​​ ​FLIP IT MORE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Flip it MORE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, you missed the table.​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it, Devan!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yesss! LAST ONE!​ ​​
​​​ ​A minute! MINUTE!​ ​​
​​​ ​LAST ONE!​ ​​
​​​ ​Little harderrrr!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You got this!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAAHHHH!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHHhhhH!​ ​​
​​​ ​LET'S! GOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEEES! LET'S GOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Only one more team is moving on.​ ​​
​​​ ​You got it, Evaaaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEEESS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go, go, GO, GO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Go, go, go!​ ​​
​​​ ​Bailey! Bailey!​ ​​
​​​ ​If you land this, your team moves on.​ ​​
​​​ ​You GOT THIS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh, I'm SO good at that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GO!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEEEESSS!​ ​​
​​​ ​awhhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​YES!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEEEESS!!​ ​​
​​​ ​waahhh!!!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YESS!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEEAAHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​So many of you, I grew up watching, ​ ​​
​​ ​and it's, like,​ ​​
​​​ ​I hate seeing you lose.​ ​​
​​​ ​Collins!!​ ​​
​​​ ​It's all right.​ ​​
​​​ ​We weren't ready for this, but…​ ​​
​​​ ​It's gonna be okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Blue team, you've been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​All that muscle for nothin'!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't even get to FLIPPP!​ ​​
​​​ ​I didn't even get a CHANCEE!​ ​​
​​​ ​AGGHHhhhH!​ ​​
​​​ ​AHHHhhhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, NOO! I grew up watching you guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​Nooo ho!​ ​​
​​​ ​I was subscribed to all of y'all ​ ​​
​​ ​for, like, yearsss.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like TEN years.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no, Fousey!​ ​​
​​​ ​Who's gonna prank everyone?​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHh!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOoaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Switch the floor back.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll give you some time to chill.​ ​​
​​​ ​What challenge are y'all gonna ​ ​​
​​ ​throw at us next?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whatever it is, we're ready for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Top ten would be incredible.​ ​​
​​​ ​Winning just seems a bit… ​ ​​
​​ ​unfathomable right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think that I worry about ​ ​​
​​ ​Ali-A and Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, everybody!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Can I have you around the money?​ ​​
​​​ ​This next game requires a little bit ​ ​​
​​ ​of setting up.​ ​​
​​​ ​BRING IN THE CURTAINS!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, man…​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-oh…​ ​​
​​​ ​It sounds like a… freaking train…​ ​​
​​​ ​is here.​ ​​
​​​ ​BRRRAAAAA​ ​​
​​​ ​Was it like a hearing challenge?​ ​​
​​​ ​BWAaaa​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like they're making noise ​ ​​
​​ ​just to make noise.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think-- ​ ​​
​​ ​I think they're messing with us.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is that true?​ ​​
​​​ ​We've been hearing weirddd sounds.​ ​​
​​​ ​Honored to be considered a YouTube legend.​ ​​
​​​ ​It feels like some sort of ​ ​​
​​ ​weird high school reunion.​ ​​
​​​ ​I remember when five million subs ​ ​​
​​ ​was the biggest deal.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're at 500 MILLION subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​How does that feel, Jimmy?​ ​​
​​​ ​It feels surreal.​ ​​
​​​ ​It doesn't feel real, to be honest.​ ​​
​​​ ​brrrRRRRR​ ​​
​​​ ​bwwWAAAAaa​ ​​
​​​ ​What is going on out there?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know, but I'm nervous.​ ​​
​​​ ​ARE YOU GUYS READY ​ ​​
​​ ​for the next game?​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on!​ ​​
​​​ ​Behind this curtain are hundreds ​ ​​
​​ ​of mannequins.​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​What???​ ​​
​​​ ​AGHhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​When the curtains drops, ​ ​​
​​ ​you have to identify​ ​​
​​​ ​which five of these mannequins ​ ​​
​​ ​are actually people.​ ​​
​​​ ​The first fifteen of you to ​ ​​
​​ ​enter your answers correctly,​ ​​
​​​ ​move on.​ ​​
​​​ ​And the other fifteen will be eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOOHH! Let's get it.​ ​​
​​​ ​To make it a little easier on you ​ ​​
​​ ​because it's, uhh,​ ​​
​​​ ​you know, a trip down ​ ​​
​​ ​memory lane…​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna play the Harlem Shake.​ ​​
​​​ ​And when the beat drops,​ ​​
​​​ ​the five humans will move slightly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Isn't the Harlem Shake copyrighted?​ ​​
​​​ ​We reached out, and we got the rights.​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOWW!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Get into position!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're about to begin.​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ Do the Harlem Shake. ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you guys working ​ ​​
​​ ​together to make​ ​​
​​​ ​this the fifteen that move on?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!​ ​​
​​​ ​Of course.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone sweeps in ​ ​​
​​ ​a clockwise direction,​ ​​
​​​ ​so that way we're not duplicating.​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't worry…​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll give you my correct numbers.​ ​​
​​​ ​he he heehe…​ ​​
​​​ ​mwaAA HA HAA HA​ ​​
​​​ ​Now, why'd he laugh like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HA HAHA…​ ​​
​​​ ​Why is he still laughing like that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Play the Harlem Shake!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do this!​ ​​
​​​ ​DROP THE CURTAINS!​ ​​
​​​ ​When the beat drops,​ ​​
​​​ ​five of these mannequins ​ ​​
​​ ​are going to move.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you input their numbers, ​ ​​
​​ ​you move on.​ ​​
​​​ ​Remember, it's only the first fifteen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Only the first fifteen.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get riiiight into it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, did you see any movement?​ ​​
​​​ ​No one's working solo.​ ​​
​​​ ​They formed teams​ ​​
​​​ ​that are spread out looking ​ ​​
​​ ​at all the mannequins.​ ​​
​​​ ​Seventeen?​ ​​
​​​ ​Get outta here, Rice!​ ​​
​​​ ​How many do you guys have?​ ​​
​​​ ​We have three.​ ​​
​​​ ​You have three?​ ​​
​​​ ​They have three of the five.​ ​​
​​​ ​What numbers you guys got?​ ​​
​​​ ​You got three?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Guys, guys! Back of the wall.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's a fourth one.​ ​​
​​​ ​One-oh-four!​ ​​
​​​ ​I got that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Remember this song?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bro…​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm just taking answers off people.​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAT IS IT?! ​ ​​
​​ ​What's the last one?​ ​​
​​​ ​With groups working together,​ ​​
​​​ ​it didn't take long for ​ ​​
​​ ​the first YouTuber​ ​​
​​​ ​to lock in all their answers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Last one, last ONE!​ ​​
​​​ ​One-oh-four!​ ​​
​​​ ​Forty-two.​ ​​
​​​ ​DONE! Check!​ ​​
​​​ ​NICE!​ ​​
​​​ ​But their teammates ​ ​​
​​ ​weren't the only ones​ ​​
​​​ ​trying to copy their answers.​ ​​
​​​ ​FOUR spots remain!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Forty-two??​ ​​
​​​ ​YESS!​ ​​
​​​ ​COME ONNN!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh!! We DID it!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOOOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on, TAYYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHHhhhh, NAHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You weren't on their team?​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I saw them do number forty-two,​ ​​
​​​ ​popped it in-- GREEN!​ ​​
​​​ ​I wasn't on their team either!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​I stole it from them.​ ​​
​​​ ​They TOOK your spot!​ ​​
​​​ ​I did! I ran back to get it.​ ​​
​​​ ​We did it, bro.​ ​​
​​​ ​Dang, so did Jelly!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, my Godddd.​ ​​
​​​ ​Reveal the mannequins!​ ​​
​​​ ​He's hitting a Fortnite emote on you.​ ​​
​​​ ​How does that make you feel?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's SOO tough, bro.​ ​​
​​​ ​The number one trick shotter to ever live.​ ​​
​​​ ​Number one vlogger to ever live.​ ​​
​​​ ​So many OG's goneeee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Before you leave, like…​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you gonna make a comeback​ ​​
​​​ ​or are you just disappearing ​ ​​
​​ ​for another five years?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm out, bro.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, I guess we'll see him ​ ​​
​​ ​in five more years.​ ​​
​​​ ​I used to watch your vlogs ​ ​​
​​ ​alllll the time!​ ​​
​​​ ​Smile More is GONE.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to join FaZe clan!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are gone!​ ​​
​​​ ​Clown gang, like, BRO! ​ ​​
​​ ​My childhood.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are just leaving?​ ​​
​​​ ​Dang, that's toughhhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​URGHhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Goodbye, ladies and gentlemennnn…​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone!!​ ​​
​​​ ​UnBELIEVABLE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​Close!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was close. It was epic!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​It was epic.​ ​​
​​​ ​The VANOSS crew!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're all out now.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was team Vanoss over Speedy--​ ​​
​​​ ​nooOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Even Casey…​ ​​
​​​ ​Casey… NO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOOoo!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOoooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​YOU'RE not crying.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'M crying.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jimmyyy…​ ​​
​​​ ​It breaks my heart to leave, but…​ ​​
​​​ ​Doesn't pain meee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's jump into the next game!!​ ​​
​​​ ​wooOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you guys ready?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's gooo, BABY!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOOOO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​yeahHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Final FIFTEEN!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh, we're in the final fifteen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Final fifteeeeen!!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's what I'm sayin'!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're in the fin--​ ​​
​​​ ​We're in the final fifteen!​ ​​
​​​ ​Final FIFTEEEN!!​ ​​
​​​ ​♪ Chocolate rainnnn… ♪​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHHhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOAA, WHoa, whoa, whoaaaa…​ ​​
​​​ ​Whoa.​ ​​
​​​ ​What just happened?​ ​​
​​​ ​He pushed me OUT!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's it??​ ​​
​​​ ​Gone…​ ​​
​​​ ​Byeee!​ ​​
​​​ ​YOOOooo!!​ ​​
​​​ ​ahhHHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You were already out, though.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, but I was tryna sneak in.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think-- I think he caught.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, well, anyways, ​ ​​
​​ ​I'll see ya later.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uhh, all right.​ ​​
​​​ ​Byeee!​ ​​
​​​ ​I love you, mom.​ ​​
​​​ ​Top fifteen! How's it feeeel?​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHHHhhH!​ ​​
​​​ ​wOOOO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaddya say…​ ​​
​​​ ​we eliminate another nine of you?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, woowww…​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAT??​ ​​
​​​ ​BRING IT IN!!​ ​​
​​​ ​What is that?​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaaat?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, God. It's all happening.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it's gonna be ​ ​​
​​ ​a floor memory thing.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm STRESSED!​ ​​
​​​ ​And up next....​ ​​
​​​ ​Floor... is lava.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHhhH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is dopeee!​ ​​
​​​ ​You know the deal.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you touch the lava, ​ ​​
​​ ​you're eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​But here's the twist.​ ​​
​​​ ​I need you to handcuff yourselves ​ ​​
​​ ​into groups of three.​ ​​
​​​ ​Brooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​Noo!​ ​​
​​​ ​What!?​ ​​
​​​ ​Choosing your team is entirely up to you.​ ​​
​​​ ​But it could decide your fate ​ ​​
​​ ​in this game.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm goin' Ali, all the way.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm good with you guys.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm down.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'reee us three!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, us three right here!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're a team. We're a team.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're team captain, I guess.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you gonna go middle?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yahh, I guess I'm team captain.​ ​​
​​​ ​YOLO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​yolo…​ ​​
​​​ ​Handcuff positions are locked in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Each team...​ ​​
​​​ ​will get two of these circles.​ ​​
​​​ ​Step on it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Place the other one,​ ​​
​​​ ​and do that until you get across.​ ​​
​​​ ​And if at any point you touch the lava,​ ​​
​​​ ​your entire team is eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you remember how BIG ​ ​​
​​ ​this trend was back in the day?​ ​​
​​​ ​I know it!​ ​​
​​​ ​We played it as kids!​ ​​
​​​ ​Like we would put pillows ​ ​​
​​ ​down on the floor.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's address the elephant in the room.​ ​​
​​​ ​Why they all have helmets.​ ​​
​​​ ​You, uhhh, fell earlier.​ ​​
​​​ ​I did fall earlier… but I'm great.​ ​​
​​​ ​You made a Floor is Lava video.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​How many years ago?​ ​​
​​​ ​Bro, like, 6-7.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah…​ ​​
​​​ ​ahh HAHA HAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​haha ha!!​ ​​
​​​ ​First two teams to get to this side ​ ​​
​​ ​without touching the lava move on!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Three…​ ​​
​​​ ​Two…​ ​​
​​​ ​One!​ ​​
​​​ ​GO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​If any of your teammates ​ ​​
​​ ​touch the lava,​ ​​
​​​ ​your ENTIRE team is eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Philip DeFranco's team is moving over ​ ​​
​​ ​to one circle together,​ ​​
​​​ ​pushing the next one forward, ​ ​​
​​ ​and then moving over.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali is literally carrying ​ ​​
​​ ​his teammate on his back.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is craaazy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meanwhile Marques' team ​ ​​
​​ ​is trying to scoot.​ ​​
​​​ ​Left now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Is this strat gonna work?​ ​​
​​​ ​Don't go so faaaast​ ​​
​​​ ​that you end up being the reason ​ ​​
​​ ​someone else instantly wins.​ ​​
​​​ ​We can take our time a little.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, yeah, yeahhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Take our time. Take our time!​ ​​
​​​ ​huuHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NO, no, noo! Got you!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, thank you--​ ​​
​​​ ​GOT YOU!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, THANK YOU!​ ​​
​​​ ​You're good, you're good, you're good.​ ​​
​​​ ​They're in the LEAD!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, my goshhh.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're almost here!!​ ​​
​​​ ​DON'T ruin it now!​ ​​
​​​ ​Boys in the back, ​ ​​
​​ ​you gotta catch up!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do something DRASTIC!​ ​​
​​​ ​Linus and Marques!​ ​​
​​​ ​Right now, GO!​ ​​
​​​ ​Marques' and Jacksfilms' teams ​ ​​
​​ ​are waaayyy behind.​ ​​
​​​ ​OhHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, come on, TOUCH IT!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on--​ ​​
​​​ ​We got our first team!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHHhhH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​We got our FIRST TEAM!!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next team to cross still ​ ​​
​​ ​moves on to the next challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly's team and Coby's team ​ ​​
​​ ​are neck and neck.​ ​​
​​​ ​Here we go-- ​ ​​
​​ ​We got this, we got this.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's NECK AND NECK!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHO'S gonna join 'em?​ ​​
​​​ ​JELLY!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You-- Are you jumping?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, OHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​WAIT, wait--​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know who it was.​ ​​
​​​ ​After reviewing the footage…​ ​​
​​​ ​On this iPad, I have the team ​ ​​
​​ ​that crossed first.​ ​​
​​​ ​And as you see…​ ​​
​​​ ​YES!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A crossed,​ ​​
​​​ ​and Chad also accidentally ​ ​​
​​ ​touched the lava.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, WHAAT?!​ ​​
​​​ ​woOAHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​We DID it!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​The co-founder of YouTube himself​ ​​
​​​ ​has been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Change the floor!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sorry, boysss…​ ​​
​​​ ​You've been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Aghh, mannn…​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck, y'all!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, y'all…​ ​​
​​​ ​BYE!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Sooo many big names.​ ​​
​​​ ​Win the MILLION!​ ​​
​​​ ​Man…​ ​​
​​​ ​If we have tech issues, ​ ​​
​​ ​we're now screwedddd.​ ​​
​​​ ​YEP, yep.​ ​​
​​​ ​Before you leave, ​ ​​
​​ ​I just wanna say​ ​​
​​​ ​thank you for making ​ ​​
​​ ​such an amazing platform.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Appreciate you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Appreciate it.​ ​​
​​​ ​He's pretty cool!​ ​​
​​​ ​YouTube allowed every single ​ ​​
​​ ​person here to change their lives.​ ​​
​​​ ​and connect with billions of ​ ​​
​​ ​people all over the world.​ ​​
​​​ ​And because of you,​ ​​
​​​ ​we are here and able to do ​ ​​
​​ ​whatever this video is.​ ​​
​​​ ​He's the guy!​ ​​
​​​ ​This is the MANN!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks, Jimmy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Take care.​ ​​
​​​ ​Appreciate it, good luck!​ ​​
​​​ ​I came to the Motrin Recharge Lounge,​ ​​
​​​ ​AKA, where we're holding ​ ​​
​​ ​all the eliminated contestants​ ​​
​​​ ​to tell 'em they will be ​ ​​
​​ ​playing a part​ ​​
​​​ ​in the final game.​ ​​
​​​ ​How you guys enjoying ​ ​​
​​ ​the Motrin Lounge?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's dopeee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Relaxing.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a viiibe.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know you guys are eliminated,​ ​​
​​​ ​but thanks to our friends at Motrin,​ ​​
​​​ ​they created the ​ ​​
​​ ​Motrin Recharge Lounge​ ​​
​​​ ​for everyone to get some relief and reset.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which is good because ​ ​​
​​ ​I need you guys to recharge​ ​​
​​​ ​because you're coming back ​ ​​
​​ ​for the final challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​What??​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone eliminated is coming back ​ ​​
​​ ​for the final challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are gonna have ​ ​​
​​ ​an opportunity to decide​ ​​
​​​ ​which one of those people ​ ​​
​​ ​ends up winning.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaaat?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's insaaane!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm kind of willing to do anything for ​ ​​
​​ ​a million dollars at this point.​ ​​
​​​ ​hehh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I made it this far, so…​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, Motrin!​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys rest up,​ ​​
​​​ ​and I'll see you at the end ​ ​​
​​ ​of the video.​ ​​
​​​ ​All riiight!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you!​ ​​
​​​ ​We're down to the final six.​ ​​
​​​ ​Not every YouTube legend ​ ​​
​​ ​can make it to this video,​ ​​
​​​ ​which is why... ​ ​​
​​ ​I reached out to the Sidemen​ ​​
​​​ ​and I let them pick the next challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​OH, goshhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHhhhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Wassup, LEGENDS?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Look, when they sent me the clip,​ ​​
​​​ ​KSI was still in the Sidemen.​ ​​
​​​ ​I know he just left.​ ​​
​​​ ​Not really sure what to do about it,​ ​​
​​​ ​sooo I'm just gonna ignore it ​ ​​
​​ ​and still use the clip.​ ​​
​​​ ​NOW!​ ​​
​​​ ​We all want to see you eat​ ​​
​​​ ​THE WORLD'S HOTTEST CHIP.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOOHHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHAA HAHA HA HAAAA!!​ ​​
​​​ ​NOooooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHHhhH!​ ​​
​​​ ​For this next game,​ ​​
​​​ ​there will be one person on ​ ​​
​​ ​each side of this podium.​ ​​
​​​ ​One of you will have the choice​ ​​
​​​ ​between eating a hot chip ​ ​​
​​ ​or a not hot chip​ ​​
​​​ ​and that person on the other side,​ ​​
​​​ ​if they guess correctly ​ ​​
​​ ​which one you eat,​ ​​
​​​ ​moves on, and you're eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​If they guess incorrectly,​ ​​
​​​ ​you move on, and they're eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​How do we decide who eats ​ ​​
​​ ​or who does not eat?​ ​​
​​​ ​That's a GREAT question!​ ​​
​​​ ​The person with the ​ ​​
​​ ​oldest public upload​ ​​
​​​ ​on their YouTube channel is May.​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHH! What does that mean?​ ​​
​​​ ​May, which side do you want?​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you wanna eat the chip​ ​​
​​​ ​or react to the person ​ ​​
​​ ​eating the chip?​ ​​
​​​ ​I want to…​ ​​
​​​ ​eat the chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on up!​ ​​
​​​ ​And next! You have to pick ​ ​​
​​ ​one of these five competitors.​ ​​
​​​ ​It's either you…​ ​​
​​​ ​or them that goes home.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh…​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOAaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Woowww…​ ​​
​​​ ​Why did you pick me? ​ ​​
​​ ​I need to know.​ ​​
​​​ ​I just picked you ​ ​​
​​ ​'cuz you're in the middle.​ ​​
​​​ ​You just picked him ​ ​​
​​ ​'cuz he was in the middle?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-huh…​ ​​
​​​ ​huh haha ha hee!!​ ​​
​​​ ​And while the rest of us turn around,​ ​​
​​​ ​May will decide if she's actually ​ ​​
​​ ​going to eat the hot chip,​ ​​
​​​ ​hoooo…​ ​​
​​​ ​rated at over two million units ​ ​​
​​ ​on the Scoville scale.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okayyy…​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, everyone, turn back around.​ ​​
​​​ ​Go for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, gosh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, my Goddd.​ ​​
​​​ ​She took a MASSIVE bite.​ ​​
​​​ ​All riiight.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did she eat the spicy chip​ ​​
​​​ ​or the not spicy chip?​ ​​
​​​ ​pffff…​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH, my gosh.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, my GOD.​ ​​
​​​ ​You keep taking your eyes off of her.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're only intel is right here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at her face. ​ ​​
​​ ​Is it telling you ANYthing?​ ​​
​​​ ​She's poker facing it.​ ​​
​​​ ​She looks like she's struggling.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like mentally?​ ​​
​​​ ​HMmm?!​ ​​
​​​ ​She looks like she's focusing ​ ​​
​​ ​TOO hard​ ​​
​​​ ​on trying to make it look like​ ​​
​​​ ​it's not spicyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, really?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go with just ​ ​​
​​ ​the logical answer​ ​​
​​​ ​'cuz I really can't get ​ ​​
​​ ​much from her.​ ​​
​​​ ​She's gone for the non-spicy one.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your final answer is non-spicy?​ ​​
​​​ ​PFFFfff…​ ​​
​​​ ​May…​ ​​
​​​ ​was this the not spicy chip?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, WHAT??!​ ​​
​​​ ​ohHHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​He got it riiight!​ ​​
​​​ ​And I'm out…​ ​​
​​​ ​YESSsss!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A is MOVIN' ON!!​ ​​
​​​ ​And May… is eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for comin' out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank youuuu!!​ ​​
​​​ ​The next oldest upload…​ ​​
​​​ ​is Cute Girl Hairstyles.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh, my gosh.​ ​​
​​​ ​A generation of women grew up​ ​​
​​​ ​learning how to style ​ ​​
​​ ​their hair from her.​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you wanna react?​ ​​
​​​ ​Or do you wanna be in the hot seat?​ ​​
​​​ ​Literally.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't wanna eat it.​ ​​
​​​ ​You don't wanna eat it?​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, then come around. ​ ​​
​​ ​Come over here!!​ ​​
​​​ ​So that means…​ ​​
​​​ ​you get to choose ​ ​​
​​ ​which one of these guys​ ​​
​​​ ​DOES eat it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Did Jelly say that he likesss hot stuff?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't mind it.​ ​​
​​​ ​He doesn't mind it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeahhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​That's such a nonchalant answer.​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHA!! HAA HAHA HAH!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAAaa haaa…​ ​​
​​​ ​hehh HEHE HEEE HEE HEHEE!​ ​​
​​​ ​hnnn huh huh haha haa…​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, you gotta pick.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooohh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do it.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!​ ​​
​​​ ​Take a look at which one's which.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay!​ ​​
​​​ ​Whenever you're ready…​ ​​
​​​ ​it's the Jelly show.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, he just ate the entiiiire chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​And now she is analyzing ​ ​​
​​ ​EVERY emotion in his face​ ​​
​​​ ​to try to get a read.​ ​​
​​​ ​Staring at his eyessss…​ ​​
​​​ ​ahhHH haha hah hoo! hehhh!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Well…​ ​​
​​​ ​that just made it a little weird, ​ ​​
​​ ​but--​ ​​
​​​ ​There's no sweating.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're not crying.​ ​​
​​​ ​Every little thing you do influences ​ ​​
​​ ​what she decides.​ ​​
​​​ ​Anything you want to say to her?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be honest…​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to be on this seat.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oohhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​So she gave you what you wanted?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeahhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​But I also got what I wanted.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I get a video.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're all winnin'!​ ​​
​​​ ​Do you think he's trying to trick you?​ ​​
​​​ ​I mean, if he ate the spicy ​ ​​
​​ ​and he didn't react AT all…​ ​​
​​​ ​he's prettyyy good.​ ​​
​​​ ​You want to lock it in?​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't knowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​heehhHH…​ ​​
​​​ ​huUUHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go not spicy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Not spicy!​ ​​
​​​ ​Which did you eat?​ ​​
​​​ ​Spicy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you serious??​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​WHATT?!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOAAaAAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​UGHh…​ ​​
​​​ ​WOWOW HAH HA!!​ ​​
​​​ ​That was pretty hot. ​ ​​
​​ ​It was pretty hot.​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHA HAH!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm kinda dying. ​ ​​
​​ ​Can I have the milk now?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes!! Go for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​All riiiight, we're GOOD.​ ​​
​​​ ​We're goooood.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your poker face was SO gooood!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WOoo!​ ​​
​​​ ​Kudos on the acting skills.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly is movin' on!​ ​​
​​​ ​MATE, I did NOT know that.​ ​​
​​​ ​You have been eliminated.​ ​​
​​​ ​I knowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm so sorry, you guysss.​ ​​
​​​ ​*cough cough*​ ​​
​​​ ​Philip DeFranco's oldest video is 2017,​ ​​
​​​ ​and your oldest video is 2010.​ ​​
​​​ ​Meaning… you get to pick.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Are you eating or reacting?​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna have, uhhh,​ ​​
​​​ ​my friend Phil eat the chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, really?!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, Phil, come on up.​ ​​
​​​ ​So why did you want him ​ ​​
​​ ​eating the chip instead of you?​ ​​
​​​ ​You put the power in his hands.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't want to go through ​ ​​
​​ ​what he's goin' through.​ ​​
​​​ ​*cough cough*​ ​​
​​​ ​bluAHH OUAHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, I'm struggling.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right, everyone, turn around, ​ ​​
​​ ​face this way.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let us know.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​That was quick. Wow…​ ​​
​​​ ​The FINAL spot in ​ ​​
​​ ​the FINAL game​ ​​
​​​ ​is decided right now.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, he's-- ​ ​​
​​ ​he's just going for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​OOFff--​ ​​
​​​ ​That looks spicyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let you chew it.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​You know…​ ​​
​​​ ​Let it SOAK in.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mhmm…​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you tried the Feastables ​ ​​
​​ ​chocolate milk?​ ​​
​​​ ​I haven't.​ ​​
​​​ ​What do you think of Feastables?​ ​​
​​​ ​I kind of want some. ​ ​​
​​ ​I haven't eaten a chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, there's some ​ ​​
​​ ​Feastables chocolate milk.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​*gulp gulp GUUULPP*​ ​​
​​​ ​Duuude, you need to try this.​ ​​
​​​ ​There's some right there for you.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wait, are you helping me ​ ​​
​​ ​promote my product,​ ​​
​​​ ​or are you trying to trick him ​ ​​
​​ ​into drinking it?​ ​​
​​​ ​A little bit of both.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've eaten the spicy chip before.​ ​​
​​​ ​eeuuHHH heh heehhh..​ ​​
​​​ ​Breathing was…​ ​​
​​​ ​BAD.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Breathing.​ ​​
​​​ ​hnhh!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah…​ ​​
​​​ ​hhhooo!​ ​​
​​​ ​HOT.​ ​​
​​​ ​So when he did that breath, ​ ​​
​​ ​what'd you notice?​ ​​
​​​ ​He keeps closing his mouth.​ ​​
​​​ ​Your eyes are glossy, brooo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeah. Wait-- ​ ​​
​​ ​Stare into those eyes.​ ​​
​​​ ​But you're not really sweatinggg!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hmm…​ ​​
​​​ ​Awhh, MAN!!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't tell!​ ​​
​​​ ​See if you can cut through the noise.​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a chip that was eaten ​ ​​
​​ ​that was not spicy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Then we had a spicyyy--​ ​​
​​​ ​Mhmm.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ooohh…​ ​​
​​​ ​So my mind's pulling me ​ ​​
​​ ​that you just didn't do spicy.​ ​​
​​​ ​My FINAL answer…​ ​​
​​​ ​Uh-huh?​ ​​
​​​ ​I believe you ate…​ ​​
​​​ ​UMmm…​ ​​
​​​ ​The Regular Chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Spicy Chip.​ ​​
​​​ ​hUHH!​ ​​
​​​ ​And you're-- you're dying right now?​ ​​
​​​ ​No.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was on hot ones, mannn. ​ ​​
​​ ​It was easy.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's HOT.​ ​​
​​​ ​UGHhhh, Phil!​ ​​
​​​ ​I looove spicy. I need to--​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH, my gosh.​ ​​
​​​ ​I need to FEEL it.​ ​​
​​​ ​All right… JC.​ ​​
​​​ ​No milk??​ ​​
​​​ ​No, I'm good.​ ​​
​​​ ​UGhhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, wowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​Look at that!​ ​​
​​​ ​And you three will be competing ​ ​​
​​ ​in the FINAL GAME​ ​​
​​​ ​for one MILLION DOLLARS ​ ​​
​​ ​for one of your fans.​ ​​
​​​ ​haha hah haa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Insane.​ ​​
​​​ ​If I manage to get ​ ​​
​​ ​the one million dollars,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd love to give back to my community ​ ​​
​​ ​through gaming equipment,​ ​​
​​​ ​gaming consoles for those ​ ​​
​​ ​that aren't as fortunate.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think I'd take 20,000 dollars, ​ ​​
​​ ​split it across fifty people.​ ​​
​​​ ​I would rebuild the entire video ​ ​​
​​ ​that we're doing right now​ ​​
​​​ ​inside of a video game, ​ ​​
​​ ​and let my community battle it out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Probably give 50,000 dollars ​ ​​
​​ ​away at a time.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ready for the million dollar game?​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, my God-- Yeaahh!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm ready for it.​ ​​
​​​ ​How are we gonna take a trip ​ ​​
​​ ​down memory lane​ ​​
​​​ ​without hitting the BIGGEST GAME ​ ​​
​​ ​in YouTube history?​ ​​
​​​ ​Wooooww!​ ​​
​​​ ​The game that started my career.​ ​​
​​​ ​The game that started ​ ​​
​​ ​so many careers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whaat??​ ​​
​​​ ​BRING IT IN!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAAT!?​ ​​
​​​ ​It's a Minecraft!​ ​​
​​​ ​In this game, you will have access to ​ ​​
​​ ​a bunch of Minecraft building materials.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, my GOODness.​ ​​
​​​ ​Minecraft is the most popular ​ ​​
​​ ​video game in the world,​ ​​
​​​ ​and was actually my first ​ ​​
​​ ​video on this channel.​ ​​
​​​ ​It shaped the platform into ​ ​​
​​ ​what it is today.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many Minecraft videos have you made?​ ​​
​​​ ​Probably 2,000.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many have you made?​ ​​
​​​ ​Probably 2,000 as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Zero.​ ​​
​​​ ​aHAHA HAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, well…​ ​​
​​​ ​You have one hour to build ​ ​​
​​ ​the best Minecraft house you can​ ​​
​​​ ​and then we will bring back all ​ ​​
​​ ​of the eliminated YouTubers​ ​​
​​​ ​from this video to vote ​ ​​
​​ ​on the best build.​ ​​
​​​ ​Whichever one has the most votes,​ ​​
​​​ ​will win their fans one MILLION dollars.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wowww…​ ​​
​​​ ​ALL RIGHT!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Three!​ ​​
​​​ ​Two…​ ​​
​​​ ​One.​ ​​
​​​ ​BEGIN BUILDING!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Taking five at a timeee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wow! Phil is getting riiight into it.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have an idea, and that's ​ ​​
​​ ​to build a treehouse.​ ​​
​​​ ​That would be amazing.​ ​​
​​​ ​You want the person to ​ ​​
​​ ​be able to come in,​ ​​
​​​ ​and it feels nice on ​ ​​
​​ ​the inside as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​And guys, don't forget to look ​ ​​
​​ ​in your chest!​ ​​
​​​ ​You have a crafting table.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is everything inside their chest.​ ​​
​​​ ​We've got some fences.​ ​​
​​​ ​We got some flowers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone is super locked in ​ ​​
​​ ​on their builds right now,​ ​​
​​​ ​but honestly, all of them have ​ ​​
​​ ​a long way to go.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no, nooo. ​ ​​
​​ ​Sorry, sorryyy, SORRY.​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, no. OHH, no… ​ ​​
​​ ​Oh, nooo.​ ​​
​​​ ​Is it like this now? ​ ​​
​​ ​I could kick your's over!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh, no…​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH! Ohh--​ ​​
​​​ ​You got NOTHIN'!​ ​​
​​​ ​Noo, no. I'm-- ​ ​​
​​ ​I'm chilling.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm chilling. I'm chilling.​ ​​
​​​ ​You got NOTHIN'!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Million dollars on the lineeee.​ ​​
​​​ ​Build some rose bushes maybe?​ ​​
​​​ ​My son would be very happy.​ ​​
​​​ ​Not just 'cuz it's Minecraft, ​ ​​
​​ ​but he is a big gardener.​ ​​
​​​ ​I try to play with my kids.​ ​​
​​​ ​They run circles around me,​ ​​
​​​ ​and they're just like, "DAAAADD!"​ ​​
​​​ ​I underestimated how ​ ​​
​​ ​long it would take​ ​​
​​​ ​to put the blocks just… together.​ ​​
​​​ ​HALF the time has gone by.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali's getting there.​ ​​
​​​ ​Phil has a fortress.​ ​​
​​​ ​And Jelly… maybe has a tree.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know what Jelly's trying ​ ​​
​​ ​to pull off hereee.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll be honest--​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know what that is either.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna be honest…​ ​​
​​​ ​me neither!!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's good news, okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​And while they're building,​ ​​
​​​ ​the CEO of YouTube has ​ ​​
​​ ​a surprise for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​We'll be right back.​ ​​
​​​ ​Neal!​ ​​
​​​ ​Jimmyyy, good to see you!​ ​​
​​​ ​We have a special surprise to celebrate ​ ​​
​​ ​500 million subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Wowww.​ ​​
​​​ ​You ready to see it?​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's do it-- ​ ​​
​​ ​YESS! I'm ready!​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay, let's take a look.​ ​​
​​​ ​WHOAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, my GOSH! ​ ​​
​​ ​And it's our color, too!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's right, yes.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is AWESOMEEE!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, thank you! ​ ​​
​​ ​And obviously…​ ​​
​​​ ​thank you to every single one of you ​ ​​
​​ ​that subscribed.​ ​​
​​​ ​I meannn, I have a lot I wanna say,​ ​​
​​​ ​but I'll save it for ​ ​​
​​ ​the end of the video.​ ​​
​​​ ​For now, let's go see who wins!​ ​​
​​​ ​The clock is TICKING.​ ​​
​​​ ​Something semi-good is better ​ ​​
​​ ​than something not finished.​ ​​
​​​ ​YOUTUBERS, you officially have ​ ​​
​​ ​five minutes remaining.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is little Jimmy the Bee.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh! This is the bee's house.​ ​​
​​​ ​If you build a regular house, ​ ​​
​​ ​it's harder to stand out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly, your's looks SICK!!​ ​​
​​​ ​You think so?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, it looks good, mate.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm a bit worried.​ ​​
​​​ ​Me and Phil's are very close.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly's is unique.​ ​​
​​​ ​I think it just comes down ​ ​​
​​ ​to personal taste.​ ​​
​​​ ​Everyone, you have ONE MINUTE!​ ​​
​​​ ​One of these builds…​ ​​
​​​ ​will win a MILLION DOLLARS ​ ​​
​​ ​for their subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, CRAP.​ ​​
​​​ ​When that timer hits zero,​ ​​
​​​ ​no more stacking, no more laying, ​ ​​
​​ ​no more moving.​ ​​
​​​ ​No more ANYthing.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ten, nine, eight!​ ​​
​​​ ​Seven! Six, five, four…​ ​​
​​​ ​At the beginning of this video,​ ​​
​​​ ​we had 50 YouTubers that ​ ​​
​​ ​shaped this platform​ ​​
​​​ ​to be what is is today.​ ​​
​​​ ​but now there are only--​ ​​
​​​ ​Three!​ ​​
​​​ ​Two!​ ​​
​​​ ​One!​ ​​
​​​ ​STOP! No more touching.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm done.​ ​​
​​​ ​The BUILDS are FINAL.​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's get all the eliminated ​ ​​
​​ ​YouTubers to vote.​ ​​
​​​ ​I don't know… ​ ​​
​​ ​I don't think I got this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who do you think's gonna win?​ ​​
​​​ ​I feel like that.​ ​​
​​​ ​Mmm… WOW.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Who better to give the first vote ​ ​​
​​ ​than CAPTAIN SPARKLEZ?!​ ​​
​​​ ​Arguably the most famous ​ ​​
​​ ​Minecraft YouTuber to everrr liveee!​ ​​
​​​ ​Pressure to be the firsttt oneee.​ ​​
​​​ ​How many hours would you say ​ ​​
​​ ​you have in Minecraft?​ ​​
​​​ ​Like… a yearrrr.​ ​​
​​​ ​So you are MORE than qualified ​ ​​
​​ ​to judge Minecraft Houses.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've seen a few.​ ​​
​​​ ​Come on over here. ​ ​​
​​ ​We'll start with Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Welcome to my Minecraft build.​ ​​
​​​ ​This right here is… tree house.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, we do have an entry.​ ​​
​​​ ​So for example, any foxes…​ ​​
​​​ ​Right.​ ​​
​​​ ​or any squirrels that want ​ ​​
​​ ​to go up into the tree,​ ​​
​​​ ​we have a beautiful ladder with ​ ​​
​​ ​an entryway on the side.​ ​​
​​​ ​Now let's hear from Ali-A.​ ​​
​​​ ​Trees on either side, ​ ​​
​​ ​some plants on the outside.​ ​​
​​​ ​And if we make our way in, ​ ​​
​​ ​we can close the doorsss…​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohhh, yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​keeping the mobs out ​ ​​
​​ ​whilst we stay inside​ ​​
​​​ ​and let the night cycle pass.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then when the mobs are gone, ​ ​​
​​ ​we open it back up.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then Philip DeFranco.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yes, sir.​ ​​
​​​ ​The one with the least ​ ​​
​​ ​Minecraft experience here.​ ​​
​​​ ​Have you played Minecraft before?​ ​​
​​​ ​So actually that's why this is this build.​ ​​
​​​ ​Right? So I have maybe forty logged hours.​ ​​
​​​ ​My son loves to give me crap.​ ​​
​​​ ​He yelled at me when I used ​ ​​
​​ ​the wrong wood,​ ​​
​​​ ​and so even this is, like, ​ ​​
​​ ​just for him.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is pretty much our ​ ​​
​​ ​first build together.​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh, man…​ ​​
​​​ ​This is a tough decision!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm impressed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Which build did you like the most?​ ​​
​​​ ​I think...​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A has...​ ​​
​​​ ​the most ​ ​​
​​ ​impressive structure.​ ​​
​​​ ​YESSss!​ ​​
​​​ ​One point for Ali-A.​ ​​
​​​ ​And as more and more YouTubers ​ ​​
​​ ​cast their vote…​ ​​
​​​ ​Philip DeFranco.​ ​​
​​​ ​I gotta go with Ali-A's house.​ ​​
​​​ ​A vote for ALI!​ ​​
​​​ ​Oh, yeahhh, Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'mma go with Ali-A's house.​ ​​
​​​ ​I choose Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​I gotta go with Aliiii.​ ​​
​​​ ​I've gotta go with Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm giving it to Ali!​ ​​
​​​ ​It seemed that some of them preferred ​ ​​
​​ ​the structure Ali made.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's Minecraft architecture.​ ​​
​​​ ​That's where my vote is.​ ​​
​​​ ​You're going for Ali-A?​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah.​ ​​
​​​ ​Others liked Phil's connection ​ ​​
​​ ​with his son.​ ​​
​​​ ​I gotta go with the feeeeels, dude.​ ​​
​​​ ​That means a lot to me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go Phil as well.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, the-- the story, just like,​ ​​
​​​ ​it's just so touching.​ ​​
​​​ ​Like, with your sonnn,​ ​​
​​​ ​you've built this thing and​ ​​
​​​ ​he's gonna see this video, and yeah…​ ​​
​​​ ​I think, out of all the three builds,​ ​​
​​​ ​I like Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​Jelly!​ ​​
​​​ ​You are my first vote, my BROTHER!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah, you got my vote.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you, bro!​ ​​
​​​ ​All right!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Out of 31 votes, Jelly has one, so…​ ​​
​​​ ​Honestly Jelly you could probably ​ ​​
​​ ​just leave with them.​ ​​
​​​ ​HA HAAA HAh HAaa HAH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHA Haahaa haha!​ ​​
​​​ ​LISTEN, listennn.​ ​​
​​​ ​hahaha haaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​Calm down now, Jimmy, ​ ​​
​​ ​all right??​ ​​
​​​ ​Lemme stick it out ​ ​​
​​ ​'til the end of this.​ ​​
​​​ ​Okay.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was like, okayyy,​ ​​
​​​ ​I need to do something unique ​ ​​
​​ ​to try and stand out.​ ​​
​​​ ​Well, they already voted…​ ​​
​​​ ​I know, but--​ ​​
​​​ ​HAHA HAH HAA!​ ​​
​​​ ​I-- you know--​ ​​
​​​ ​HAH HAHA HA HA haaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​I'll let them know!​ ​​
​​​ ​And it didn't work out.​ ​​
​​​ ​But Phil and Ali-A were virtually tied.​ ​​
​​​ ​I gotta give it to Ali-A.​ ​​
​​​ ​I… pick… Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A's got this in the BAG.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I have to give it to Philip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-Aaaa.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna have to go ahead ​ ​​
​​ ​and vote for Philip.​ ​​
​​​ ​Ali-A.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have to go with Ali-- ​ ​​
​​ ​I'm SORRY Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm s-- I'm SORRY.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm SORRYYY!​ ​​
​​​ ​Purple flowers, ​ ​​
​​ ​what I saw first,​ ​​
​​​ ​and purple flowers-- ​ ​​
​​ ​flowers remind me of…​ ​​
​​​ ​my cat, Nyla, who just passed.​ ​​
​​​ ​Awhh…​ ​​
​​​ ​I love your-- your's, and I pick you.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm looking at a tree with torches on it ​ ​​
​​ ​that's about to burn down.​ ​​
​​​ ​A house with no lighting inside​ ​​
​​​ ​that's gonna spawn zombies ​ ​​
​​ ​and kill 'em.​ ​​
​​​ ​And then this one that worksss.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'mma go with Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna vote for Ali-A's house.​ ​​
​​​ ​Phil's got the biggest house, ​ ​​
​​ ​so it's easy for me.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm gonna go… Phil.​ ​​
​​​ ​And with all the votes cast…​ ​​
​​​ ​oohhHHHH!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHhh! WHOAaa!​ ​​
​​​ ​WooOOO!!!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHHH HOhoo ho hooOO!​ ​​
​​​ ​I do not condone this.​ ​​
​​​ ​OKAYY, we have the results!​ ​​
​​​ ​The one MILLION dollar winner…​ ​​
​​​ ​is…​ ​​
​​​ ​not Jelly.​ ​​
​​​ ​You, uhhh, got, like, no votes. ​ ​​
​​ ​I'm sorry.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thanks for having me, Jimmy.​ ​​
​​​ ​You were some FIERCE competitors.​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank youuu.​ ​​
​​​ ​I love both of your houses.​ ​​
​​​ ​I have NO idea who's got this.​ ​​
​​​ ​The winner, though, is one of you two.​ ​​
​​​ ​A million dollars to your subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck!​ ​​
​​​ ​Good luck.​ ​​
​​​ ​The winner...​ ​​
​​​ ​of a million dollars ​ ​​
​​ ​for their subscriber is…​ ​​
​​​ ​PHILIP DEFRANCO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WHAAT?!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHhh, my GOD!​ ​​
​​​ ​OHH, MY GODDD!!​ ​​
​​​ ​WOOOoooOOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Let's GOOOoooOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​Thank you guys!​ ​​
​​​ ​PHILIP! PHILIP! PHILIP!​ ​​
​​​ ​Ohh, NOO!!​ ​​
​​​ ​AHHhhH!​ ​​
​​​ ​PHILIP! PHILIP! PHILIP!​ ​​
​​​ ​That's crazyyy.​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't believe you did this!​ ​​
​​​ ​I can't believe it either.​ ​​
​​​ ​I was almost out ​ ​​
​​ ​on the first challenge.​ ​​
​​​ ​Yeah!​ ​​
​​​ ​How are you gonna give away ​ ​​
​​ ​the million dollars to your subscribers?​ ​​
​​​ ​We're gonna do 20,000, fifty times.​ ​​
​​​ ​YEAHhhHH!!​ ​​
​​​ ​20,000, fifty times!​ ​​
​​​ ​Hey, guys, before you leave the video,​ ​​
​​​ ​I wanted to say something from ​ ​​
​​ ​my childhood bedroom​ ​​
​​​ ​where before I had 500 million subscribers,​ ​​
​​​ ​actually, one day, ​ ​​
​​ ​I had zero subscribers.​ ​​
​​​ ​This is where I created my channel​ ​​
​​​ ​and, umm, partially why ​ ​​
​​ ​I wanted to do this video​ ​​
​​​ ​where I gave a nod to all these ​ ​​
​​ ​OG YouTubers that came before me.​ ​​
​​​ ​Because when I was a little kid ​ ​​
​​ ​in this bedroom,​ ​​
​​​ ​a lot of these creators,​ ​​
​​​ ​I used to watch them ​ ​​
​​ ​every single day.​ ​​
​​​ ​And, uhhh, I just wanna one more time, ​ ​​
​​ ​just say thank you​ ​​
​​​ ​to the 50 creators ​ ​​
​​ ​that came out.​ ​​
​​​ ​You guys are all amazing, ​ ​​
​​ ​everyone was super kind,​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm very grateful for all of you.​ ​​
​​​ ​And I also just wanna say thank you ​ ​​
​​ ​to all of you that watch the videos​ ​​
​​​ ​because without you guys ​ ​​
​​ ​watching these videos,​ ​​
​​​ ​I wouldn't be able to build wells ​ ​​
​​ ​around the world,​ ​​
​​​ ​feed people in need.​ ​​
​​​ ​I wouldn't be able to ​ ​​
​​ ​do the good I do,​ ​​
​​​ ​even if it was still just ​ ​​
​​ ​a handful of you watching,​ ​​
​​​ ​even if most of yous went away​ ​​
​​​ ​and it was just me right now ​ ​​
​​ ​talking to ten of you…​ ​​
​​​ ​I'd still be grinding YouTube.​ ​​
​​​ ​I-- I love this more than ​ ​​
​​ ​you could ever imagine.​ ​​
​​​ ​I'm beyond blessed to have ​ ​​
​​ ​this many viewers.​ ​​
​​​ ​In closing, ​ ​​
​​ ​I just want to say​ ​​
​​​ ​I will never take you guys ​ ​​
​​ ​for granted.​ ​​
​​​ ​And, umm, thanks for watching.​ ​​